He's not looking for trouble...he's wearing it.
The Tuxedo is a thriller, action, comedy film directed by Kevin Donovan.
Cabbie-turned-chauffeur Jimmy Tong learns there is really only one rule when you work for
playboy millionaire Clark Devlin : Never touch Devlin's prized tuxedo.
But when Devlin is temporarily put out of commission in an explosive accident, Jimmy puts on the tux
and soon discovers that this extraordinary suit may be more black belt than black tie.
Paired with a partner as inexperienced as he is,
Jimmy becomes an unwitting secret agent.
Jimmy Tong, played by Jackie Chan.
Del Blaine, played by Jennifer Love Hewitt.
Clark Devlin, played by Jason Isaacs.
Steena, played by Debi Mazar.
Dietrich Banning, played by Ritchie Coster.
Dr. Simms, played by Peter Stormare.
The Tuxedo is a 2002 American science fiction action comedy film directed by
Kevin Donovan and starring Jackie Chan and Jennifer Love Hewitt.
The spy parody involves a special tuxedo that
grants its wearer superhuman abilities.
The plot surrounds a corporate terrorist who threatens to poison the United States' fresh water supply
with bacteria that spills electrolytes into the blood and totally dehydrates the host.
The film received negative reviews from critics upon release and earned
a total worldwide box office gross of $104.4 million.
The film explores themes of new york city, martial arts, chauffeur, bomb, spy.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking and intense.